{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","address":"34 W Grand River","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Eli Boyer","licenseNumber":"226472","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"3/1/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Plan Review","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000009C7B5B2522C354C0B006A240C22A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41896","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","inspectionDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"3","pfcount":"3","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"CHEMICAL STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41896","inspectionDate":"4/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 135 degrees f to 70 degrees F for more than 2 hours","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize shallow pans, ice baths, agitation, or quick chilling to cool food items."}]},{"inspectionid":"41644","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","inspectionDate":"2018-02-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","inspectorid":"80","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41644","inspectionDate":"2/28/2018","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"At the Drain line","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"41644","inspectionDate":"2/28/2018","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"41644","inspectionDate":"2/28/2018","inspectionType":"Pre-opening","establishmentid":"51622578","name":"Lover's Only","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622578"}}